Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
- Box: 62, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: 1966 Ars Pensionsuppgorelser SAF-SIF, SAF-SALF, SAF-HTF, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Svenska Arbetsgivareforeningen
  - Item 8: Rapport Sur L'Assurance-Vieillesse et Survivants Federale Durant L'Annee, 1959; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Office Federal des Assurances Sociales
  - Item 9: Spaarquote en Welvaartvast Pensioen, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: A. Van Doorn
  - Item 10: Weldhen Beitrag Wahle Idh?, 1964; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Asgard- Verlag
  - Item 11: L'Assurance Vieillesse Des Salaries, 1968; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Bernard Feuilly
- Box: 62, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Die Pensions-Dynamik, 1966; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Author: Osterreichischen Gewerkschaftsbundes
- Box: 62, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Canada Pension Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Author: Canada Department of National Health and Welfare
  - Item 2: Guideposts to Pension Planning, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Author: The Canadian Chamber of Commerce
  - Item 3: Canada Pension Plan Bill C-75, 1964; Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Author: Commerce Clearing House
    Notes: March 19, 1964
  - Item 4: Quebec Pension Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Notes: June 1, 1965
  - Item 5: Retirement Pensions, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Author: Government of Canada
  - Item 6: The Canada Pension Plan and Changes in the Old Age Security Act, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Box: 62, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Effect on Occupational Pension Schemes of Future Increases in the Benefits of the State Scheme, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 10)
    Author: Insurance Institute of London
  - Item 2: Pensions, Publication (Box 62, Folder 10)
    Author: L.R.D. Publications Ltd.
  - Item 3: In Place of Beveridge?, Publication (Box 62, Folder 10)
    Author: Geoffrey Howe
- Box: 62, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Report of the Indiana Appointed to Investigate the Question of Old Age Pensions, Publication (Box 62, Folder 11)
    Author: Indiana Appointed to Investigate the Question of Old Age Pensions
- Box: 62, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Old Age Plans and Programs of Farmers, 1949; Publication (Box 62, Folder 12)
    Author: T.N. Hurd
  - Item 2: Social Security, Publication (Box 62, Folder 12)
    Author: New York Department of Audit and Control
- Box: 62, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Ontario Portable Pension Plan Legislation, 1966; Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
    Author: C.C.H. Canadian Limited
  - Item 2: Ontario Portable Pension Plan Legislation, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Box: 62, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Provisions of the Old-Age, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Ways and Means
    Notes: July 30, 1965
  - Item 2: The Insured Pension Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
    Author: New York Institute of Life Insurance
  - Item 3: Hospital Insurance Coverage of Aged Beneficiaries, 1962; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: National Survey of Old-Age and Survivors Insurance Beneficiaries, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Oasdi Digest, 1971; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
    Notes: April 1971
  - Item 6: Employment, 1971; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Fact Sheet No. 20, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
    Notes: December 1946
  - Item 8: Fact Sheet No.19, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Legislative History of the Coverage Provisions, 1951; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
    Author: Wilbur J. Cohen
    Notes: June 1951
- Box: 62, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Your New Social Security, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
    Author: U.S. Federal Security Agency
- Box: 62, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Old-Age and Survivors Insurance, 1948; Publication (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Old Age Income Assurance, 1966; Publication (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Box: 62, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Pensions: A Problem of Management, 1928; Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
    Author: Edward S. Cowdrick
  - Item 2: Tax Help for the Self-Employed, 1962; Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
    Notes: October 12, 1962
  - Item 3: Reduction of Retirement Benefits Dut to Social Security Increases, 1967; Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
    Notes: August 21, 1967
  - Item 4: The Social Security Retirement Test for Farm People, 1961; Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
    Author: U.S. Department on Health, Education, and Welfare
  - Item 5: Disclosure of Official Records and Information, 1967; Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Box: 62, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Summary of the Provisions of the Old-Age, Survivors, and Disability Insurance System, the Hospital Insurance System, and the Supplementary Medical Insurance System, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Title II of the Social Security Act, Publication (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Replacement for Lost Earnings, 1962; Publication (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: When You're 65, Publication (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Box: 62, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Economic Assumptions, Publication (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Box: 62, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Parameters of Aging, Publication (Box 62, Folder 20)
    Author: Don F. Heisel
- Box: 62, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: the State and its Senior Citizens, 1959; Publication (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Salute to the Aging, 1958; Publication (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Government Payments, Publication (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: A Summary of 1965 New York State Legislation Affecting the Aging, Publication (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Box: 62, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Guidelines to Organization of County Committees on Aging, 1962; Publication (Box 62, Folder 22)
    Author: North Carolina Governor's Coordinating Committee on Aging
    Notes: August 1962
- Box: 62, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Filial Responsibility in the Modern American Family, Publication (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Box: 62, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Our Aging Population, Publication (Box 62, Folder 24)
    Author: T. Lynn Smith, D.G. Marshall
- Box: 62, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Older Employee in Industry, 1933; Publication (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Aging and Employability, 1948; Publication (Box 62, Folder 25)
    Author: Ewan Clague
    Notes: July 22, 1948
  - Item 3: Taking a Look at the Age Factor in Employment, 1949; Publication (Box 62, Folder 25)
    Author: Phyllis H. Moehrle
    Notes: March 7, 1949
  - Item 4: The Social and Economic Problems of Employment of Older Workers, 1949; Publication (Box 62, Folder 25)
    Notes: July 21, 1949
  - Item 5: Employment Problems of Older Workers in New York City, 1950; Publication (Box 62, Folder 25)
    Notes: August 1950
- Box: 62, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Rehabilitation of the Aged and the Older Disabled Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 26)
    Author: West Virginia Division of Vocational Rehabilitation
  - Item 2: Age, Physical Ability, and Work Potential, Publication (Box 62, Folder 26)
    Author: Leon F. Koyl
  - Item 3: Age Barriers to Employment, 1962; Publication (Box 62, Folder 26)
    Author: Texas Legislative Council
- Box: 62, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Aging Worker in the Canadian Economy, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
    Author: Canada Deparment of Labour
- Box: 62, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Company Practices Regarding Older Workers and Retirement, Publication (Box 62, Folder 28)
    Author: Edwin Shields Hewitt and Associates
  - Item 2: Conclusions of the Manpower and Social Affairs Committee on Policies for the Employment of Older Workers, 1967; Publication (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Company Practices Regarding Older Workers and Retirement, 1952; Publication (Box 62, Folder 28)
    Author: National Metal Trades Association
    Notes: February 1952
- Box: 62, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Employment Aspects of the Economics of Aging, 1969; Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Employment and Retirement of Older Workers, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
    Author: California Governor's Commission on the Employment and Retirement Problems of Older Workers
- Box: 62, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: How to Use Older Workers, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 30)
    Author: Mill and Factory
    Notes: April 1957
- Box: 62, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Middle-Aged and Older Workers Full Employment Act of 1968, Publication (Box 62, Folder 31)
    Notes: November 1968
  - Item 2: The Older Worker in the Federal Service, 1961; Publication (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: Mr. Employer Here's How You Can Get Better Results with Older Workers, Publication (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: Meet the Over 40 Worker, Publication (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: Meeting the Manpower Challenge of the Sixties with 40-Plus Workers, 1960; Publication (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Box: 62, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Preparation of Indutrial Workers for Retirement, 1952; Publication (Box 62, Folder 32)
    Author: Arthur J. Noetzel
    Notes: March 20, 1952
  - Item 2: Production at Any Age, Publication (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Box: 62, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Utilization of Older Professional and Scientific Workers, 1961; Publication (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: When You've Lost a Job After Forty, 1964; Publication (Box 62, Folder 33)
    Author: Walter Morris
  - Item 3: Rulings Interprative of the Age Provisions of the Law Against Discrimination, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 33)
    Author: New York Commission for Human Rights
- Box: 62, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Older Workers Face a Plant Shutdown: South Bend Report, 1964; Publication (Box 62, Folder 34)
    Author: National Council on the Aging
  - Item 2: Who Are the "Over 45" Unemployed?, 1963; Publication (Box 62, Folder 34)
    Author: Alton C. Johnson, Thomas R. Hoffmann, Robert C. Miljus
  - Item 3: A Study of the Employment Problems of the Older Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 34)
    Author: Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination
  - Item 4: Proceedings of the Institute on the Older Worker, 1961; Publication (Box 62, Folder 34)
    Author: University of Hawaii
- Box: 62, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Employeurs et Travailleurs Ages, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    Author: Universite de Liege
- Box: 63, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Employability of the Older Person, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Author: The Personnel Club of New York
  - Item 2: The Older Worker in Industry: List of References, 1929; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: July 1929
  - Item 3: Industrial Gerontology, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Box: 63, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Rehabilitation of the Older Disabled Worker - the Academician's Responsibility, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: How to Eliminate Age Barriers to Employment, 1959; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: February 20, 1959
- Box: 63, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Not Too Old at Sixty, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Author: National Corporation for the Care of Old People
  - Item 2: Ageing and the Semi-Skilled, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Author: Great Britain Medical Research Council
  - Item 3: The Later Working Life in the Building Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Author: F. Le Gros Clark
  - Item 4: The Working Fitness of Older Men, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: The Employment Problems of Elderly Men, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The Elderly Worker, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Author: Industrial Welfare Society
  - Item 7: Ageing on the Factory Floor, 1957; Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Ageing Men in the Labour Force, 1955; Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Bus Workers in Their Later Lives, 1957; Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: New Jobs for Old Workers, 1955; Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Box: 63, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Rulings Interpretive of the Age Provisions of the Law Against Discrimination, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Older Worker, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Box: 63, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Gammal I Jobbet, 1968; Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Author: Personaladministrativa Radet
- Box: 63, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Equilibrium and Size in Static Cournot Oligopoly, 1963; Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Author: M. McManus
- Box: 63, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Facts and Figures, Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Author: Ontario Federation of Labour
  - Item 2: Facts and Figures, Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Box: 63, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Impact of the Equalization of Industrial Opportunity Program, 1969; Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Author: Stevenson & Kellogg
- Box: 63, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Preliminary Population Projections, Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Box: 63, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Open Shop Primer, 1918; Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    Author: Jacob Nathan
    Notes: July 27, 1918
- Box: 63, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Closed or Open Shop, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Author: Elbert Hubbard
  - Item 2: the Philosophy of the Closed Shop in Action, 1920; Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Author: James A. Emery
    Notes: November 17, 1920
  - Item 3: Labor Conditions and the Open Shop in Indianapolis, 1920; Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Author: Orlando B. Iles, Andrew J. Allen
    Notes: February 17, 1920
  - Item 4: Is Organized Labor Slipping?, 1919; Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Author: Dorr E. Felt
    Notes: December 13, 1919
  - Item 5: The Open or Closed Shop, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Author: Citizens Alliance of Minneapolis
  - Item 6: Closed Shop and Open Shop Terminology, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Author: New Jersey Chamber of Commerce
  - Item 7: Sherman Act, 1914; Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Box: 63, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Open Shop Number, 1921; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Author: Finance & Industry
    Notes: February 19, 1921
  - Item 2: Bulletin, 1925; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Author: Business Men's Association
    Notes: March 28, 1925
  - Item 3: The Real Labor Problem, 1921; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Author: Charles Aubrey Eaton
    Notes: March 31, 1921
  - Item 4: Independent American Shop, 1921; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Author: J.M. Vollmer
    Notes: July 1921
  - Item 5: To Employers' Organizations Everywhere, 1921; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Author: Associated Employers of Indianapolis
    Notes: September 12, 1921
  - Item 6: Invitational Announcement Nineteenth Annual Meeting, 1923; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: January 29, 1923
  - Item 7: An Un-American Condition in an All American City, 1921; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Author: W.S. Frye Transfer
    Notes: November 16, 1921
  - Item 8: Another Matter of "Business Principle", 1921; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Author: Anderson Federal System of Bakeries
    Notes: November 22, 1921
  - Item 9: Re: Anti-Picketing Ordinance, 1923; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: March 12, 1923
  - Item 10: Omaha Taxpayers Benefit by Open Shop, 1925; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Author: Business Men's Association of Omaha
    Notes: July 1925
  - Item 11: Resolution #5, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: July 19, 1922
  - Item 12: Resolution No. 1-4, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: July 17, 1922
  - Item 13: The Railroad Strike, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: July 7, 1922
  - Item 14: Letter, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: July 20, 1922
  - Item 15: Reminder No. 3, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: February 6, 1922
  - Item 16: Reminder No. 4, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: February 9, 1922
  - Item 17: Building and the Public, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: February 16, 1922
  - Item 18: Concerning the Railroad Situation, 1921; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: August 11, 1921
  - Item 19: Union Membership and Labor Day Parade, 1921; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: September 9, 1921
  - Item 20: C.I. & W.R.R. Maintains Open Shop, 1921; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: August 13, 1921
  - Item 21: Closed Shop or Open, 1923; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Author: Harvard University
    Notes: December 13, 1923
  - Item 22: Copy of Letter to the Chief of Police of Indianapolis, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: July 6, 1922
  - Item 23: Insist Upon Independent Labors' Right to Work, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: July 27, 1922
  - Item 24: The Growth and Prosperity of Indianapolis, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Item 25: Reminder No. 4 - Annual Meeting, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: March 16, 1922
  - Item 26: Industrial Relations in the Chicago Building Trades, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: March 22, 1922
  - Item 27: An Open Letter to the Architects, Building Contractors and Property Owners of Indianapolis, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: February 22, 1922
  - Item 28: An Open Letter, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: March 2, 1922
  - Item 29: Which Will You Have, Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Item 30: Building and the Public, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Item 31: Urgent and Important, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Item 32: The Functioning of Public Utilities, Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Item 33: Digging Down to the Taproot of the Trouble, 1922; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Author: Employing Printers Association of America
    Notes: March 25, 1922
  - Item 34: Closed Shop or Open, 1923; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Author: Eliot
  - Item 35: Industrial Indianapolis, 1924; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: January 28, 1924
  - Item 36: Ticket Requisition, 1924; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: February 8, 1924
  - Item 37: Last Call, 1924; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: February 1924
- Box: 63, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Handbook of the American Plan Open Shop, 1926; Publication (Box 63, Folder 13)
    Author: American Plan-Open Shop Conference
    Notes: May 26-28, 1926
- Box: 63, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: High Spots in Capital-Labor Situation Today, Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Author: Ralph M. Easley
  - Item 2: Open Shop, 1931; Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Notes: November 30, 1931
- Box: 63, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Truth About the Open Shop, Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Author: Employing Photo-Engravers Association of America
  - Item 2: The Answer to Mis-Statements of Union Leaders, Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Box: 63, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Objective of Industrial Indianapolis, Publication (Box 63, Folder 16)
    Author: Andrew J. Allen
  - Item 2: Open Shop Publications, Publication (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Declaration of Principles, Publication (Box 63, Folder 16)
    Author: Associated Employers of Utica
  - Item 4: Anti-Picketing and Anti-Boycotting Law or City Ordinance, Publication (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: National Emergency Calls for Action, Publication (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Box: 63, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Principle of the Open-Shop, Publication (Box 63, Folder 17)
    Author: George Gunton
- Box: 63, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: You Can Talk Well, Publication (Box 63, Folder 18)
    Author: Herbert V. Prochnow
- Box: 63, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Retirement Plan of the State of Oregon, 1962; Publication (Box 63, Folder 19)
    Author: Oregon Public Employes Retirement System
  - Item 2: Compensation Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 63, Folder 19)
    Author: Oregon Civil Service Commission
    Notes: January 1, 1962
- Box: 63, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Changing Organizations, 1966; Publication (Box 63, Folder 20)
    Author: Warren G. Bennis
    Notes: February 1966
  - Item 2: The Human Nature of Organizations, Publication (Box 63, Folder 20)
    Author: J. Douglass Brown
  - Item 3: Functional Processes and Structural Relationships in Formal Organization Theory, 1967; Publication (Box 63, Folder 20)
    Author: Bob R. Owens
  - Item 4: The Committee Concept and Business, Publication (Box 63, Folder 20)
    Author: M.B. Brodie
  - Item 5: The Horizontal Dimension in Bureaucracy, Publication (Box 63, Folder 20)
    Author: Henry A. Landsberger
  - Item 6: Job Management Training, Publication (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: An Approach to More Productive Management of People, 1960; Publication (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Business Organization, Publication (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: A Reading List on Business Administration, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 20)
    Author: Dartmouth College
    Notes: June 1, 1947
  - Item 10: Behaviour in Organizations, 1970; Publication (Box 63, Folder 20)
    Author: Joan Woodward
    Notes: March 3, 1970
- Box: 63, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: A "Common Language" for Organization Charts, 1964; Publication (Box 63, Folder 21)
    Author: California Department of General Services
  - Item 2: Problems of Growth in Industrial Undertakings, Publication (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Box: 63, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Organization of American States, 1949; Publication (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Charter of the Organization of American States, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 22)
    Language: Spanish; English; Portuguese; French.
- Box: 63, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Tasks and Man Management of African Labour, Publication (Box 63, Folder 23)
    Author: Overseas Food Corporation
- Box: 63, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: How to Figure Overtime Pay, 1950; Publication (Box 63, Folder 24)
- Box: 63, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Overtime in the State Government, 1967; Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
    Author: Legislative Auditor of the State of Hawaii
- Box: 63, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Computing Overtime Pay, 1967; Publication (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Overtime Exemption for Commission-Paid Employees Under Fair Labor Standards Act, 1963; Publication (Box 63, Folder 26)
    Notes: August 2, 1963